A Guide to the Farrier Family Papers, 1894-1972
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Box 21, 1916-1968 (Bulk, 1930-1968) (Box 21)
  - Blevins, T. J. and Edna, November 1933-July 1938.
  - Blankenship, Alva, et al, July 1955-July 1958.
  - Buckland, H. O., April 1950-June 1959.
  - Buchanan, Wiley B. Jr and wife, January 1960.
  - Britts, R. L., January 1954-April 1961.
  - Brown, C. William, August 1960-March 1961.
  - Croft, Bert C., November 1933-December 1939.
  - Coburn, Mrs. Willie, January-April 1934.
  - W. G. Cline, July 1923-November 1933.
  - Collins, L. C., March 1933.
  - Collins, H. R., November 1933.
  - Cooper, Mary E., et al, July 1947.
  - Chisenhall, John F. to Stowers, John P., April 1920-May 1923.
  - Carr, Allen P., November 1933-January 1934.
  - Davis, Andy W., November 1933.
  - Dillow, Oscar, November 1933-June 1937.
  - Davis, V. T. estate, February 1956-February 1957.
  - Eaton, Vesta, John S., and Sam S., November 1933-January 1968.
  - Eaton, Edward S., January-March 1928.
  - Eaton, Charles L., undated.
  - Epling, Ernest, July-September 1943.
  - Epling, J. Francis, August 1925-January 1941.
  - Grace E. Fisher, November 1929-April 1935.
  - Federal Land Bank--Notes and titles, October 1933-February 1934.
  - Fink, W. Kent and wife, March-May 1934.
  - Farley, Clara O. & J. W., October 1933-September 1935.
  - Francis, A. J., September 1929-October 1936.
  - French, K. S., May 1924 and May 1929.
  - Farrier, F. F., March 1923-March 1945.
  - Farrier, R. H. estate, January 1940-April 1947.
  - Farrier, R. H. abstract (2 files), May 1916-November 1951, September 1940-August 1950.
  - Givens, Dan W., et al (Clover Hollow Land), November 1933-June 1960.
  - Guynn, W. J. and Annie E., November 1933.
  - Givens, B. L., October 1933.
  - Givens, H. O., June-July 1936.
  - Guthrie, William A. & John R., undated.
  - Harris, J. L., March-September 1940.
  - Harless, George W., November 1933.
  - Hale, Rufus C., January 1925-June 1939.
  - Harrell, T. B., December 1933.
  - Hoge, Chapman B., July 1934-July 1935.
  - Henderson, G. M., September 1933-January 1934.
  - Huffman, E. E., June-October 1940.
  - Hale, E. M., April 1917-May 1921.
  - Hale, D. T. & Thomas T., May 1926.
  - Hale, J. J. and Andelia A. and Edward C., March 1934-June 1963.
  - Hoge, J. T. S., November 1933-May 1950.
  - Johnson, Frank H. & J. O., March 1929-May 1941.
  - Johnston, Robert F., September 1934-March 1935.
- Box 22, 1916-1968 (Box 22)
  - Johnson, Clarence H., January 1925-April 1942.
  - Johnston, R. C., undated.
  - Johnston, Luther F., November 1938-October 1950.
  - Johnston, Emory, August 1933-August 1961.
  - Johnston, Emory and others, November 1939-June 1958.
  - Kanode, C. W., February 1925-February 1941.
  - Linkous, R.T., et al, March 1934.
  - Lucas, K. E. and G. C., January 1934.
  - Lucas, Lewis, May 1921-August 1923, July 1956.
  - Link, Oliver, et al (Spruce Run Property abstract), September-November 1961.
  - McDonald, George B., April 1932-December 1933.
  - McCoy, J. H., Ira K, and Cleo J., November 1933-February 1962.
  - Miller, Joseph B., December 1933-January 1934.
  - Mustard, Leonard C., March-August 1939.
  - Miller, T. Shannon, November 1933-January 1934.
  - Meadows, J. Earl, December 1933.
  - Morris, J. L., Jr., et al, March 1956-January 1960.
  - Morris, J. L.--Kidd Land, December 1942-April 1961.
  - Morris, Rodney S. and wife, November 1956-December 1959.
  - Newton, Dr. M. C., September 1934-January 1935.
  - Niday, George E., April 1934.
  - Nowlin, George W. and William B., November 1933-January 1934, February 1945.
  - Patteson, J. M, R. W., and S. A., February 1920-August 1957.
  - Patteson, W. C. and S. A., September 1929.
  - Price, George W., November 1933-April 1951.
  - Price, William C., Jr., March-April 1939.
  - Price, W. Mason, January-February 1935.
  - Peters, Harry B. and Anna, November 1923-March 1924.
  - J. M. Rogers, undated.
  - Riggs, G. Milton, December 1933-September 1939.
  - Reynolds, M. W., February 1925-September 1933.
  - Robertson, Aubrey B., May 1929-January 1934.
  - Robertson, Paul M., June 1957-May 1968.
  - Stafford, Jess W., July 1962.
  - Mark B. Smith v. F. W. Bull-Dunklee Store Property (Newport), October-November 1950.
  - Spangler, A. H., et al, December 1940-January 1941.
  - Songer, George J., March 1934-May 1941.
  - Stephens, William R., July-August 1935
  - Sands, D. McKinley, December 1934-February 1935.
  - Stafford, C. A. and Mary, December 1933.
  - Stafford, Joe P., April-July 1954.
  - Shannon, Mary and Minnie, January 1926-November 1941.
  - Stafford, Irving and Gilbert, November 1933.
  - W. H. Thompson (Pearisburg sheriff charged with shooting and killing a bootlegger) v. Commonwealth, May 1925-July 1926.
  - Stafford, Dailey V., December 1922.
  - Woods, Frank H., April 1950-October 1958.
  - Williams, Warren D. and S. S., August 1948.
  - Williams, J. J. and Lydia, April 1934-October 1960.
  - Williams, Elliott B., January 1934-November 1958.
  - Williams, Evans N., April 1948.
  - Walker, W. Austin, May 1934-May 1939.
  - Walker, W. W., February 1934.
  - Wheeler, W. H., November-December 1933.
  - Williams, Mary Ruth, January 1934.
  - Williams, Doyle S., April 1940.
  - Williams, Donald L., November 1934-November 1947.
  - Williams, W. A., May 1916-May 1921.
  - Williams, James M., July 1929-August 1938.
  - Williams, Omer B., May 1921-July 1956.
- Box 23, 1915-1972 (Bulk, 1950-1969) (Box 23)
  With a few exceptions, most of the material in this box concerns loan contracts and land transactions.
  - Miscellaneous, April 1946-October 1972.
    Includes material found loose at the front of the box. Consists of deeds, abstracts, court briefs, contracts, and correspondence connected to the work of Andrew L. Farrier.
  - Miscellaneous, April 1915-July 1939.
    Material found loose at the front of the box. Work by Williams & Farrier or Martin P. Farrier, including deeds, title abstracts, cancelled checks, and a report on improving Mountain Lake. There are also papers concerning the estate of Percy H. Brown.
  - Ahalt, Paul Edwin, et ux., July 1953-December 1962.
  - Bales, Ivan G, et ux.-_Farmers Home Loan, June-September 1966.
  - Brewer, J. Alf, Willie Sue, and William P., June 1929, May 1951-April 1960.
  - Brock, Odell and Pillion, Bill, January 1934-April 1964.
  - Claypool, William H., June-July 1951.
  - Candler, Howard B. (FHA), January 1952-March 1953.
  - Bank of Giles Co. v. A. K. Blankenship, February 1963-July 1967.
  - Clark, William David, February 1959-July 1962.
  - Croy Motor Sales, Inc., May 1947-September 1956.
  - Dunn, Hazel F., August-October 1950.
  - Dent, Joseph F., January 1950-April 1951.
  - DeBusk, Emma M., November 1933-April 1961.
  - Duncan, Clifford H. and wife, January 1959-March 1961.
  - Dowdy, Welford W. & R. W., January 1931-April 1966.
  - Drake, William R. (Kessinger land), March-April 1968.
  - Dunbar, J. W. estate, July-September 1952.
  - Echols, Lillian (J. F. Porterfield estate), October 1947-August 1959.
  - Farley, J. F. estate, May 1969-November 1970.
  - Federal Land Bank v. W. W. Shumate, May 1929-December 1933.
  - Freeman, Eugene P. (FHA), February 1956.
  - Fletcher, Vernon A., November 1953-March 1954.
  - Frye, Ralph L., et al, November 1960-November 1967.
  - Givens-Gerberich Corporation, May 1931-December 1954.
  - Gentry, Harry A., et ux. (FHA), May-December 1953.
  - Gibboney, Trusteee, November 1938-August 1959.
  - Hoilman, et al v. Hoilman (parking lot), November 1958-March 1966.
  - Hoge v. Hoge, August 1943-January 1952.
  - Hall, Irvin H. (FHA), April-September 1952.
  - Hutchinson, Richard C., et ux., September-November 1953.
  - Hobbs, Willie W., January-April 1951.
  - Holdren, Allie (GI), October 1956-December 1957.
  - Marshall C. Huffman (title), October-November 1932, April 1955, and March 1960.
  - Hardiman, W. A., April 1926-January 1950.
  - Helton, Sylvester R. (GI), October 1956-September 1957.
  - Huffman, Harold G. (GI), September 1957-October 1958.
- Box 24, 1904-1971 (Bulk, 1950-1969) (Box 24)
  - Hoge Brothers (2 folders), August 1946-December 1950; October 1938-January 1941, July 1967.
  - Porterfield, B. W. and Hoge, Richard, June 1935-January 1961.
  - Johnson, Mirent Levi, August 1924-January 1934, November-December 1946.
  - Johnston, estate of W. F. Sr. and Lillie H., April-August 1966.
  - Keffer, Martin E., et ux. (FHA), June 1962-March 1963.
  - Killey, J. Clark, September 1941-June 1963.
  - Lucas, Robert P. (FHA), May 1952-May 1954.
  - Lake Hotel Corporation--Mountain Lake, March 1931-June 1966.
  - Link, George W. and wife, March-April 1968.
  - Lucas, J. C. estate and C. A. September 1934-August 1960.
  - L. and R. Theater Corporation Inc. Charter, June 1959-August 1960.
  - Lafon, Yaney R., et ux. (Furrow land), December 1959-May 1960.
  - Logan, C. P. (Newport land), February-July 1959.
  - Lewey, Joseph F. and wife, October 1958.
  - Newport lots, August 1955.
  - Muncy, Joe, October-November 1965.
  - Medley, J. M., October-December 1965.
  - Miller, L. L. estate, January 1912-April 1926.
  - Miller, John J., et al v. Miller, Stephen C. (Pembroke property), November-December 1966.
  - McAtic, Huldah (Hoge Store property), January 1961-February 1966.
  - National Bank of Blacksburg, February 1950-December 1971.
  - Owen, John D. (FHA), September 1950-August 1952.
  - Oney, Carolyn F., December 1952-May 1959.
  - Oney, T. J., January 1953.
  - Painter, George W., et ux. (FHA), February-March 1953.
  - Price, William C. (GI), January-December 1953.
  - F. Gilbert Porterfield, c. May 1914.
  - Pettit, Rudolph W., et ux. (FHA), February-June 1955.
  - Porterfield, A. B., September 1956-May 1967.
  - Pack, Margaret P. and Donald P., June-July 1966.
  - Psathas, Bill and George, June 1965.
  - Price, W.C. estate (Horse Shoe Farm), March 1966-January 1968.
  - Porterfield, D. R., November 1949.
  - Prillaman, Kermit E., et ux. (FHA), April 1963-January 1964.
  - Mrs. Carrie Page, guardian, May 1904.
  - Robertson, Jas A. and Forrest W., May 1922-August 1952.
  - Robertson, Statson, undated.
  - Robertson, Birdle (Land Bank), August 1922-December 1953.
  - Robinson, Lester E., December 1952-April 1954.
  - Tilmont, Carl C, et ux. (FHA) (Fort Branch), March-April 1960.
  - Young, William L. Jr and wife, November-December 1959.
  - Virginian Railway Co., August 1943-December 1945.
  - Little Stoney Game and Fish Reserve, September 1941-April 1952.
- Box 25, 1929-1972 (Bulk, 1960-1969) (Box 25)
  - Correspondence to A. L. Farrier, June 1959-March 1960.
  - H. T. Adair estate, March 1933-January 1952.
  - Claude B. Akers, September-October 1962.
  - Amos, Walter L., et ux., September-October 1968.
  - Atkins, Byron S., Harry D., and R. L., May 1962-October 1964.
  - Barnet, Preston, November 1958-July 1959.
  - Copies of deeds drawn up by A. L. Farrier, October 1959-July 1972.
  - Clark, Charles E., et ux. (FHA), undated.
  - Crawford, Cecil C., June-August 1967.
  - Chewning, W. A. estate, September 1965-February 1967.
  - Cooler, Frederick Wm., et ux., October-November 1965.
  - Copies of deeds, wills, and contracts drawn up by A. L. Farrier, July 1948-January 1972.
  - Echols, Carl L., Jr., April 1966-March 1967.
  - Edgewood Development (John and William Guthrie), March 1941.
  - Essary, E. O. and wife, May-June 1972.
  - Foote Mineral Co.--Dust matter, September 1966-April 1967.
  - F Case Files--Mary Falgaini to C. W. Furrow and wife, October 1947-October 1970.
  - Lawson, Robert A. and John C. (FHA), October 1964-February 1968.
  - Morris, C. E., et al, August-November 1961.
  - Snyder, Archie G., et ux. (FHA),September-October 1966.
  - Corell, James B. and wife (FHA), undated.
  - Harrell, Elmer E., et ux. (FHA), August 1966-January 1967.
  - Parcell, Phillip E., et ux. (FHA), September-October 1966.
  - Perdue, Arvin E., et ux. (FHA), November-December 1966.
  - Mills, Lawrence F., et ux. (FHA), December 1966-January 1967.
  - Chafin, Harold E., et ux. (FHA), January-February 1967.
  - Raynes, Harvey S., et ux. (FHA),December 1966-March 1967.
  - Tilley, Thomas O., et ux. (FHA), January-February 1967.
  - Collins, Paul B., et ux. (FHA), April-May 1967.
  - Frazier, Douglas M., et ux. (FHA), March-April 1967.
  - Allen, Billy R., et ux. (FHA), April-June 1967.
  - Marshall, Donald L., et ux. (FHA), April-June 1967.
  - Evans, Robert, et ux. (FHA),April-June 1967.
  - Martin, Marvin L,, et ux. (FHA), July-August 1967.
  - Hale, Kenneth C., et ux. (FHA), May-August 1967.
  - Williams, Jack C., et ux. (FHA), July-September 1967.
  - Farmer, Robert E., et ux. (FHA), August-September 1967.
  - Martin, Walter R., et ux. (FHA),September-October 1967.
  - Ratcliffe, Odell B., et ux. (FHA), September-October 1967.
  - Bradley, George L., et ux. (FHA), October 1967.
  - Gantier, Clarence W., et ux. (FHA), July-September 1966.
  - Smith, Billy M., et ux. (FHA), November 1967-February 1968.
  - Bartley, Ronald, et ux. (FHA), January-March 1967.
  - Gordon, Carroll C., et ux. (FHA), November 1967-February 1968.
  - Bartley, Douglas F., et ux. (FHA), February-March 1968.
  - Billips, Duane R., et ux. (FHA), July 1967-March 1968.
  - Ernest, William W., et ux. (FHA), March-April 1968.
  - Perdue, Charles F., et ux. (FHA), July-September 1966.
  - Blankenship, Charles Jr., et ux. (FHA), April-May 1968.
  - Martin, Ruby L. (FHA), March 1966-May 1968.
  - Dean, George B. Jr., et ux. (FHA), May-October 1968.
  - Pennington, Oran G., et ux. (FHA), December 1968-February 1969.
  - McCroskey, Estil K., et ux. (FHA), October 1968-July 1969.
  - Jennelle, Robert E., et ux. (FHA), October-December 1968.
  - Brown, James A., et ux. (FHA), November-December 1968.
  - McGuire, Joe C., et ux. (FHA), October-November 1968.
  - Anderson, Ellis J., et ux. (FHA), December 1968-February 1969.
  - Ganoe, Larry E.,, et ux. (FHA), February-March 1969.
  - Williams, Alfred W., et ux. (FHA), December 1966-January 1967.
  - Perkins, Roy Lee, et ux. (FHA), May-July 1969.
  - Hare, Jerry W, et ux. (FHA), June-September 1969.
  - Shires, Buddy H., et ux. (FHA), August-October 1969.
  - Sadler, Sammy (FHA), December 1969-February 1970.
  - Gusler, John D., et ux. (FHA), December 1969-March 1970.
  - Kast, Donald L., et ux. (FHA), July 1969-March 1970.
  - Epperly, Harry T., et ux. (FHA), March-April 1970.
  - Parks, Annabell and Everett (FHA_, October 1969-June 1970.
  - Sadler, Clarence H., et ux. (FHA), June-August 1970.
  - Higgs, Clarence E., et ux. (FHA), October-November 1970.
  - Ratcliff, Donald E., et ux. (FHA), September 1967-June 1968.
  - Guynn, Donald G., et ux. (FHA), January-March 1970.
  - Materials on previous owners, July 1929-November 1942.
  - Vaught, Maury S., et ux. (FHA), April-May 1968.
  - Wilson, Arthur L., et ux. (FHA), April-May 1968.
  - James A. Gray (I. E. Williams to J. E. Gray deed), December 1968.
  - F. M. Hilton deeds, October 1964-March 1965.
  - Howell, Jessie K. & E. A., deeds, July-August 1966.
  - Johnson, Albert R. and wife, May-November 1966.
  - Copies of deeds: Mr. & Mrs. J. L. Jennelle; Mr. & Mrs. W. C. Jennings; Mr. & Mrs. Mirent L. Johnson; Mr. & Mrs. Shuler J. Johnston; Mr. & Mrs. James M. Jones; Mrs. Marie S. Journell; Mr. & Mrs. Roy H. Journell, April 1960-November 1970.
  - Kessinger, Darrell W., et ux., June 1972.
  - Lafons family, January 1966-October 1969.
  - Lee Long, December 1965.
  - Lucas, C. A. v. Johnston, Julian H., January 1967 and November 1969.
  - Long, C. F. (French), June 1960-February 1965.
- Box 26, 1912-1972 (Bulk, 1950-1969) (Box 26)
  - Meadows, George E., et ux., (FHA), March 1945-April 1957.
  - Copies of deeds: Carrie A. McGuire; Robert L. Meredith; Cloyd C. Morris; C. P. Martin; Edward K. McCoy; Lacy W. Moore; S. A. Martin; Mid-State Homes, Inc.; Earnest H. Lang; W. W. Lafon; Hattie E. Miller, August 1961-April 1972.
  - Oney, Carolyn F., June 1968-May 1970.
  - Copies of deeds: Okley Albert; John Peery; J. Maurice Payne: Clarence Pfeifer; Ernest G. Porterfield; Ira ELmer Price; Miller C. Porterfield; James W. Perkins; Jottie M. Pennington; A. C. Pyrtle; W. C. Price; Pauline S. Phlegar; Olonzo C. Proffitt; Bill Pillion; Grayson D. Pettrey; James W. Price; Aldon B. Porterfield; Sidney L. Peeters; H. R. Price; William D. Parcell, February 1957-December 1968.
  - Poff Land--Sheldon, April-August 1970.
  - Parcell, S. H., October 1969-March 1970.
  - Price, A. H.--land, June 1968-May 1971.
  - Martin, E. J. and Talma L., April 1938-October 1955.
  - Puckett, Nannie C., January 1912-December 1918.
  - Federal Land Bank v. Puckett, November 1936-September 1937.
  - Deeds: Basil Radford, et al; T. S. Robertson; C. O. Rogers; Ernest B. Radford; Alice F. Runion; Donald L. Ray, et al; Thomas E. Robertson; Alice M. Ragsdale; Dallas M. Ross, July 1960-November 1969.
  - Deeds: L. K. Smith; Dexter Stevers; Harvey C. Snidow; John L. Stafford; W. D. Sanders; H. G. Smith; Veda S. Smith; N. E. Short; Bertie Saunders; Elizabeth Snidow Payne; Darcie C. Shelor; Douglas E. Shorter; Hattie L. Sadler; Cecil M. Surratt; Billy B. St. Clair; G. H. Gerrell; C. R. Smith; W. S. Smith; John S. St. Clair; Sidney M. Scott; R. C. Stafford; C. P. Scott; F. W. Smith; L. M. Smith; R. G. Simon; A. H. Spangler; H. P. Smith; P. L. Stephens; J. J. Snidow; Sallie Stanley; M. L. Spangler; C. R. Spangler; C. M. Smith; George Stevens, April 1949-July 1970.
  - Sutphin-Blankenship, Vernon, et ux., August 1969-November 1971.
  - Deeds, contracts, and court cases: Trinkle and Sobyns; David Taylor; William H. Robertson; G. C. Thomas; Clyde Tabor; C. G. Tilley; James W. Smith; Tobe Taylor; William R. Trout; Kenneth V. Turner; Alex G. Taylor; C. H. Toler; Noah M. Tickle; Alfred Tabor; H. G. Taylor; Katie M. Thacker; William M. Tabor; W. H. Thomas; Frederick D. Thompson; Dahl D. Trenor, October 1948-July 1963.
  - Thomas, Wanda and Mary Sue, October 1955-June 1972.
  - Terry, I. B and wife, March 1972.
  - Ulman, Erwin I., April-August 1951.
  - Vest, David C., November 1968.
  - Copies of wills drawn up by A. L. Farrier, July 1951-September 1970.
  - Maps and deeds: John F. Woodyard; Clarence H. Sadler; Muriel T. Wilson; Everett N. Williams, July-November 1970. Also: O. F. Vaught; Martin Viars; Kenneth P. Young, January 1948-January 1950.
  - Atkins, B. S. & H. D., July 1955-June 1070.
  - Barbour, Stuart A., Jr., August 1963-February 1969.
  - Biskin, Donald S. and wife, April-May 1972.
  - Burgess, William C. and wife, April-May 1969.
  - Butt, Howard D., et ux., May-July 1972.
  - Echols, Lillian P. and C. L., February 1962.
  - Edge, Harlan R., et ux., October 1964-August 1965.
  - Freeman, Eugene P., et ux., July 1954.
  - Fleeman, Vernice A. and Edith S., undated.
  - Dills, W. M., December 1928-July 1961.
  - Givens, James P., May 1962.
  - Foote Mining Co., March 1964.
  - Farm Home Administration (FHA), September 1962-January 1966.
  - Giller, E. Scott, et ux. (Ding property), September 1967-August 1972.
  - Gregory v. Bird, et al, December 1941-September 1951.
  - Given-Gerberich Corp., February 1951.
  - Genesco, Inc. v. Joseph H. Barnes, Jr., undated.
  - Gilmore, P. M., July 1961-February 1962.
  - Copies of deeds: H. M. and J. A. Gusler; Sarah G. and L. A. Blevins; William E. Going, April 1961-March 1962.
  - Garnishment proceeding, January 1961-August 1966.
  - Hunter, O. J., August 1966.
  - Taxes, 1959-1963.
  - Deeds: Gladys M. and S. K. Johnston; Sterling R. and Eddie Johnson; William G. Johnston; Robert F. and Edna W. Johnston; W. T. and Lucy H. Jamison, September 1955-January 1964.
  - Nannie Johnson v. Herbert Wilburn, July 1964.
  - Johnston, R. L., November 1932 and April-July 1965.
  - Johnson, Albert R., May 1937-March 1939 and May 1963-May 1966.
  - Kessinger, James L, et ux., February-March 1968.
- Box 27, 1901-1972 (Bulk, 1950-1969) (Box 27)
  - Deeds, wills, contracts and estate settlements: C. P. Logan; Earl B. Lucas; Luther Lucas; C. W. and L. K. Long Mason; C. A. Lucas; St. Paul's Lutheran Church (Newport); James D. Lafon; L. L. & J. Doak Lucas; Minor Lafon; Wilbur W. Lafon, April 1931-June 1972.
  - Deeds, wills, contracts and estate settlements: Billy Gene McCall; W. F. McCall; Joseph F. McGuire; Lucy P. McGuire; Bessie Phlegar McDonald; Robert H. McCall; E. D. McClanahan, January 1959-February 1960.
  - Deeds, wills, contracts and estate settlements: John J. Miller; Virgil Meadows; C. F. & Edward F. Mahaffey; J. R. Morris; J. L. Morris; Campbell & Melvin D. Mutter, October 1956-February 1960.
  - Mullins, Robert E., et ux. (FHA), April-May 1965.
  - Mustard, John C., Jr., et ux. (FHA), February-May 1962.
  - Mason, Bernard, D. W., & George, March 1920-September 1963.
  - Mason, Darwin A., February 1964.
  - Martin, A. P., September 1971.
  - Musgrove, James A., et ux., July 1970-March 1971.
  - Oliver, Osha, January 1962.
  - Pearisburg Motor Corporation, September 1947-May 1956.
  - Ramsey, Charles H. (G.I.), June 1951-September 1954.
  - Deeds, wills, contracts and estate settlements: Janey B. Reel; S. D. Rickman; Calla M. Roy; Charles G. Robertson, April 1959-July 1967.
  - Deeds, wills, contracts and estate settlements: A. E. Shumate, Jr.; J. E. Sutphin; Leland G. Smith; J. B. Stanley; C. G. Sarver; James H. Sartin; W. A. Stiff; G. M. Scott; Frank B. Strader, Jr.; W. D. Sanders; Clarence Shortt; Floyd A. Scott, July 1954-August 1965.
  - Straley, Chapman C. (land bank loan), March 1965-May 1967.
  - Stone, John P., Jr. (FHA), July-September 1965.
  - Saulnier, Richard, April 1966.
  - Stevers, William S., April 1966.
  - Spangler, George C. & A. H., February 1934-May 1955.
  - Sparks, Oran L. & wife, March-April 1971.
  - Stafford, Wilmeth H. & wife, September 1971.
  - Vest, John C. J., et ux., Novemer-December 1961.
  - Morgan v. N & W Railway Co. (livestock claims), May 1928.
  - Walker, Paul O., January 1954-November 1962.
  - Witten, T. F., November 1949-June 1965.
  - Deeds, will, court cases, and contracts: James Roy Williams; Elvira Williams; Juanita A & Nathan M. Hobbs; Marguerite S. Williamson; C. C. Straley; Edith G. Carper; D. r. Whittaker; Francenia C, William M., and Kenneth Williams; Robert M. Williams; Florence Woods; F. P. Wells; Ira F. Williams; W. F. Williams; A. Ward Williams, September 1954-November 1962.
  - Williams, Paul J, et ux. (FHA), February-March 1963.
  - Whittaker, Otto N., June 1957-September 1962.
  - Woodyard, Robert Raymond, et ux., April 1964-May 1967.
  - Deeds, wills, contracts, and court cases: Mrs. Grace. S. Williams; Vera B. & Randolph J. Wilburn; Nola J. Woods; William E. Williams; Charles C. Weaver; John F. Woodyard; Williams-Jamison Funeral Home; John Lee Wilson.
  - Whittaker, D. R. estate, May 1963-December 1964.
  - Deeds: Kile C. Williams, March 1967; A. P. Martin, May 1968.
  - Walker Williams, October 1932-April 1933.
  - Walker Williams-Tyler French-Manganese, October 1930-March 1931.
  - Walker Williams, November 1925-March 1933.
  - Switzer, Caleb M., Discharge, 1901.
- Box 28, 1921-1939 (Box 28)
  - W. H. Caldwell & Son, June 1932.
  - Cornett, S. M., September 1921, January 1924-February 1925.
  - Cunningham, v. McLain, et al, April 1921-May 1927.
  - Hugh Charlton v. C. C. Thompson, July 1925-April 1926.
  - Carper, E. L. v. Dink Lawson, May 1928.
  - Cecil, Helen Francis, March 1927-February 1928.
  - Flat Top Motor Co. v. L. T. Cadle, July 1931.
  - Cox Hat Co. v. People's Supply Co., April 1931-July 1932.
  - Federal Pure Foods Co. v. Wilmer Conner, October 1931.
  - C. J. Range v. Carl F. Chisenhall, February 1931-January 1932.
  - Virginia Division of UDC v. Mr. J. S. Andrews, June 1933.
  - Mrs. W. D. Carter, March 1926-March 1927.
  - Gordon Dalton & Co. v. B. T. Johnson, et al, November 1926-March 1928.
  - Gordon Dalton & Co. v. C. R. Mabe, August 1927.
  - Dix-Richardson Co. v. H. B. Shelton & Co., June 1927-November 1928.